https://www.csalliance.org/privacy-policy/

MENUMENUHome
News BriefAbout the WebsiteSite MapPrivacy Policy
The Society
News and EventsNewslettersAds and Requests
About the SocietyHistory of the SocietyServices and Benefits
Basics
Brief History of Confederate PhilatelyCollecting ConfederatesIndependent StatesConfederate Use of US PostageStamplessPostmasters’ Provisionals
General IssuesBlockade MailFlag of Truce MailPOW MailTrans-Mississippi Express MailPrivate Express Companies
Official ImprintsSemi-Offical ImprintsPatriotic CoversWallpaper CoversFakes
Confederate Postage Rates
Basic RatesFree Mail and Prepay ExemptionsAdditional Services
AS News
Authentication Certificate ApplicationReplacement Certificates
Resources
BooksMonographsConfederate Auction CatalogsStamp CatalogsBuying Lists
Periodical Archives
Confederate Stamp AlbumPeriodicals of August Dietz
The Virginia PhilatelistThe Southern PhilatelistThe New Southern PhilatelistStamp and Cover CollectingStamp and Cover Collectors ReviewThe Confederate Bulletin
Historic Archives
Confederate
Executive Branch and CongressMilitaryPostal LegislationPost Office Department
United States
US MilitaryDepartment of InteriorPost Office Department
DirectoriesOther DocumentsLinks to other Archives
Collections and ExhibitsConfederate Fake Collections
Freeland CollectionKent Collection
Confederate Censuses
Crown Illustrated Censuses
Other Archives1860-1865 Calendar
Donate
Cash ContributionsFund for the FutureSociety Legacy Program
Store
Publications for SaleCart
Members
LoginMembership RenewalGrievances
General informationThe Grievance CommitteeThe Grievance ProcessHow to submit a complaint
Your ProfileJoin the CWPS
ContactsYou are here: Home / Privacy Policy
Who we are
Our website address is: https://www.csalliance.org.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
Additional information
How we protect your data
What data breach procedures we have in place
What third parties we receive data from
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
Shopping Cart
Cart is empty $0.00
Featured Publications for Sale
Florida Postal History During the Civil War
Deane R. Briggs, MD
2018
The Springfield Facsimiles of Confederate Postage Stamps
Steven M. Roth, Francis J. Crown, Jr., and Patricia A. Kaufmann
2015
Support Our Advertisers
Recent Posts
November 21, 2020 CSA Special Meeting Ballot Results
2021 Annual Convention
Searchable CP
The Civil War Postal Exhibition & Symposium 2019
Welcome to the new Confederate Stamp Alliance website!
About the CWPS
The CIVIL WAR PHILATELIC SOCIETY is a non-sectional, non-political organization for fraternity, research and cooperation among hundreds of collectors of Civil War stamps, covers, and postal history. Email our webmaster with comments, suggestions and corrections.
Member Access
Username or Email Password Lost your password?Please enter your username or email address. You will receive a link to reset your password via email.Username or E-mail Don't have an account? Sign up
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkPrivacy policy
